leva Kaleginienė

From seller to developer





I've been working in IT industry for about six years and now my career goal is to retrain from seller to FrontEnd developer. I'm sure, that such ambitious goal is a proof of extremely high motivation and willingness to learn a lot.

77

Contact



+370 677 28390



ieva.kaleginiene@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ievakaleginiene



github.com/kaleginiene



Vilnius, Lithuania

Software skills

HTML, CSS, SASS

JAVASCRIPT

NODE.JS

VUE.JS

REACT

PHOTOSHOP

I have some experience working with developer platforms **Digital Ocean, MS Microsoft Azure** and **Firebase**. Also, i have some skills writing **SQL** code.

Experience

Sales manager

TELIA LIETUVA, AB

2016.09 - present

In this job position my duties are: Selling IT and Mobility services for medium and large B2B clients. Attending meetings with clients and project management: constructing budget and timelines.

Virtual assistant

VaMigle

2020.05 - 2020.09

I was working on a startup's process management. My duties were: SalesForce implementation, creating processes and training sales people. Also, working with Web Designer and FrontEnd developer was one of my responsibilities too.

Account manager

Baltnetos komunikacijos, UAB

2015.05 - 2016.09

In this job position my duties were: selling IT services to potential and existing B2B clients, attending meetings with client, managing portfolio of over 400 clients, project management: constructing budget and timelines.

Administrator -Sales manager

2014.12 - 2015.05

Domus Lumina, UAB

Roller Blinds, louvers etc. products salon administration, orders management, organizing timetables for foremen group.

Insurance consultant

2012.07 - 2014.12

PZU Lietuva, UAB DK

In this job position my duties were: communication face to face and over the phone with B2C clients, contracts extension and upselling, settlements monitoring, search of potential clients.



TEAMWORK	
QUICK LEARNER	
LEADERSHIP	
PLANNING	
PROJECT MANAGEMENT	

Working as a Sales manager I gained strong set of communication, team working, negotiation and problem solving skills, which is going to be advantageous for FrontEnd developer career.

Education

Code Academy

FrontEnd Course

2020.03 - present (exp. end of studies 2020.12.21) 9 month course of: HTML, CSS, Responsive design, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SaSS, Node.js, GIT, React, Vue.js

Vilnius Gediminas Technical University Economics Bachelor, Business management specialization

2011 - 2015

Other courses

Code Academy

Digital skills training

2020.03 - present (exp. end of studies 2020.12.21).

3 month course of: WebDesign, HTML & CSS basics, WordPress, SEO, eCommerce.

Coursera

Modern JavaScript: ES6 Basics

8 hours

8 hours of JavaScript basics, where I've learnt JS major

features of ES6.

Coursera

Web development

5 weeks

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

Women Go Tech

Atrask technologijas

3 months

3 month course about Tech industry